blogpaws.com 2016-11-28

# Privacy Policy - BlogPaws

**Terms of Use:**

By using this site, you agree to abide by the BlogPaws Editorial Guidelines.

By uploading or posting written, visual, audio, or other content on any BlogPaws blog, form, or platform, you are representing that you own or have the right to publish it and you are granting BlogPaws a permanent, non-exclusive license to display, aggregate, syndicate, or use such content for any and all purposes.

**Privacy Policy:**

Your privacy is important to BlogPaws.com. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that BlogPaws.com collects, and the ways in which BlogPaws.com uses that personal information.

**Personal information collection**

BlogPaws.com may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website;
  * information that you provide for the purpose of registering with the website (including registration information for conferences and other events, downloading files, and other purposes);
  * information about transactions carried out over this website;
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services; and
  * any other information that you send to BlogPaws.com.

**Using personal information**

BlogPaws.com may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * publish information about you on the website;
  * send to you products that you purchase;
  * supply to you services that you purchase;
  * send you statements and invoices;
  * collect payments from you; and
  * send you marketing communications.

Where BlogPaws.com discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

We may share information between and among Pet360, Inc., and its current and future parents, affiliates, subsidiaries, companies under common control and ownership, divisions and designees.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, BlogPaws.com may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**

BlogPaws.com will take reasonable technical and organizational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

BlogPaws.com will store all the personal information you provide on secure servers owned and operated by reputable web service providers, including but not limited to TypePad.com and Eventbrite.com. BlogPaws does not own or maintain web servers and provides its services via third-parties.

Information relating to electronic commerce transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology provided by our third-party web service providers.

**Cross-border data transfers**

Information that BlogPaws.com collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which BlogPaws.com operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, some personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Updating this statement**

BlogPaws.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**California**

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [BlogPawsTeam@blogpaws.com](mailto:BlogPawsTeam@blogpaws.com) or write us at: Pet360, Inc., Attn: BlogPaws Privacy Policy, 2260 Butler Pike, Plymouth Meeting, PA 19462.

**Children**

Our website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to the website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not provide any information on this website or on or through any of its features/register on the website, make any purchases through the website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [BlogPawsTeam@blogpaws.com](mailto:BlogPawsTeam@blogpaws.com) or write us at: Pet360, Inc., Attn: BlogPaws Privacy Policy, 2260 Butler Pike, Plymouth Meeting, PA 19462.

Cookies and Tracking

Cookies are small data files that one of our servers sends to your computer via your Web browser when you connect with our Web site. Their primary function is to help us remember returning customers by tracking their browsing sessions, which enables us to collect non-personally identifiable information. With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit.

Currently, our systems do not recognize browser “do-not-track” signals.  Most browsers, however, allow you to refuse cookies. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Certain portions of our Website may not be accessible to you if you disable cookies.  Please see [3rd Party Advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) for information about how you may opt-out of targeted advertising. **  
**

**Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.

BlogPaws.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Contact BlogPaws.com**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or BlogPaws.com’s treatment of your personal information, please write to: Pet360, Inc., Attn: BlogPaws

  * by email to BlogPawsTeam@blogpaws.com; or
  * by mail to Pet360, Inc., Attn: BlogPaws, 2260 Butler Pike, Plymouth Meeting, PA 19462.

**Effective Date:   August 11, 2014**
